export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Which unit is the main ground combat unit for the Terran race?",
    answers: ["Zealot", "Marine", "Zergling", "Stalker"],
    correctAnswer: "Marine",
  },
  {
    question: "What building is required to train Terran Ghosts?",
    answers: ["Barracks", "Factory", "Starport", "Ghost Academy"],
    correctAnswer: "Ghost Academy",
  },
  {
    question: "Which race has the Overlord unit?",
    answers: ["Terran", "Protoss", "Zerg", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "Zerg",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the primary resource gathering unit for Protoss?",
    answers: ["Probe", "SCV", "Drone", "Zealot"],
    correctAnswer: "Probe",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which technology allows the Protoss to warp units directly to the battlefield?",
    answers: ["Graviton Beam", "Chrono Boost", "Warp Gate", "Hallucination"],
    correctAnswer: "Warp Gate",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the Zerg equivalent of a Barracks?",
    answers: ["Hatchery", "Spawning Pool", "Roach Warren", "Infestation Pit"],
    correctAnswer: "Spawning Pool",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Protoss unit can teleport across the map with the help of Pylons?",
    answers: [
      "Zealot",
      "Dark Templar",
      "Stalker",
      "High Templar",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "What Terran unit can transform into a Hellbat?",
    answers: ["Marine", "Marauder", "Hellion", "Thor"],
    correctAnswer: "Hellion",
  },
  {
    question: "Which building allows Zerg to mutate into Lair?",
    answers: ["Hatchery", "Spawning Pool", "Roach Warren", "Hydralisk Den"],
    correctAnswer: "Spawning Pool",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the Protoss capital ship?",
    answers: ["Carrier", "Battlecruiser", "Mothership", "Void Ray"],
    correctAnswer: "Mothership",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the Terran's flying unit that can detect cloaked units?",
    answers: ["Viking", "Banshee", "Raven", "Battlecruiser"],
    correctAnswer: "Raven",
  },
  {
    question: "Which unit can spawn Banelings in Zerg?",
    answers: ["Zergling", "Roach", "Hydralisk", "Queen"],
    correctAnswer: "Zergling",
  },
  {
    question: "What upgrade allows Zerglings to move faster?",
    answers: [
      "Metabolic Boost",
      "Adrenal Glands",
      "Centrifugal Hooks",
      "Pneumatized Carapace",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Metabolic Boost",
  },
  {
    question: "Which Protoss unit can provide temporary shields to allies?",
    answers: ["Zealot", "Sentry", "Immortal", "Phoenix"],
    correctAnswer: "Sentry",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the Zerg's heavy-hitting, siege unit?",
    answers: ["Ultralisk", "Hydralisk", "Mutalisk", "Lurker"],
    correctAnswer: "Lurker",
  },
];
